<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>
    <string name = "L"> Places </string>
    <string name = "Cine"> Cinema </string>
    <string name = "Teatro"> Theatre </string>
    <string name = "Restaurante"> Restaurant </string>
    <string name = "Rumba"> Rumba </string>
    <string name = "Turismo"> Tourism </string>
    <string name = "cine1t"> Royal Films </string>
    <string name = "cine1"> It is a familiar company that began only a theater in the heart of the city of Barranquilla,
 but it was not enough to place a new entertainment; but as a culture form hobby of Colombians;
 why through the years we have grown to expand our horizons by building new cinemas and
 shopping centers, which have allowed us to project into the future and have a presence in the top five
 film companies in Colombia.\n\nLocal 3392, the Town # 43A\n in to 10:00 p. m.
    </string>
    <string name = "cine2t"> CineMark </string>
    <string name = "cine2"> The company was declared as the display of the Year by NATO.
 Cinemark Multiplex Treasury\n\n opens in Medellin. NDC The Treasury\n
 Transversal Superior Cra 25 A No. 1 A -. Southern 45
    </string>
    <string name = "cine3t"> Cinemas Procinal </string>
    <string name = "cine3"> Being at home with friends, good food and a good home theater sound good to entertain,
 However, have you considered triple that level of experience in every way, giving them a gift they will never forget ?.
 Come to our cinemas.   \n\nCommercial nCentro North Gate (Success Bello - Niquía station)
       \nTeléfono: +57 (4) 444 2244       \nSalas: 4
    </string>
    <string name = "teatro1t"> Little Theatre</string>
    <string name = "teatro1"> The Small Theater is a theater located in Medellin Colombia declared Cultural Patrimony of this city in 1985.
 Similarly, it is based since 1986, is the Architectural Heritage and Conservation. It has two chambers: the Chamber Hall,
 with capacity of 80 people and the Main Hall, with a capacity of 500 people.
       \n\nCarrera 42 No. 50 A 12 \n (Córdoba with The Beach)  Medellin\n (57) - (4) 239 3947-269 9418
    </string>
    <string name = "teatro2t"> Prado Theatre Aguila Descalza </string>
    <string name = "teatro2"> Its headquarters is a heritage building that has become artistic, architectural and tourist reference of Medellin.
 There works a room with capacity for 460 spectators; a museum that preserves oil paintings, drawings and collages of Carlos Mario Aguirre
 and other Colombian artists and a coffee bar is a meeting point before and after the presentations. The group provides ongoing programming
 at its headquarters with their own creations and guest artists. The Barefoot Eagle since its inception in 1980 has grown from a one-man project
 of its creator Carlos Mario Aguirre, who at the beginning served as actor, playwright, director and manager of his work;
 to become a strong cultural institution dedicated to promoting the performing and visual arts.
       \n\n Address: Cra 45d # 59-1, Barrio Prado\nTeléfono. (4) 2,844,211
    </string>
    <string name = "rest1t"> El Barco </string>
    <string name ="rest1"> Excellent food and attention, pure Colombian Pacific, the best sea food found in the city\n options. lunch, only cash,
 Wi-Fi free, high chairs available, Parking available, Reservation, Seat, alcohol, takeaways, Waiter, Wine and beer is served\n\n
 Carrera 48 # 85-198. | Itagui, Medellin\n +57 4 2851090
    </string>
    <string name = "rest2t">Alá Sazón</string>
    <string name = "rest2"> A great place that makes you feel in the east, the setting and the Lebanese food is excellent. A small but charming- place
       \n\nCRA 40 # 10-A - 33 | The Town\nTelefono: +57 4 2669170
    </string>
    <string name = "rest3t"> Verdeo Restaurant </string>
    <string name = "rest3"> In the restaurant you will find Verdeo prepared exclusively with organic food, natural products,
 sustainable and most importantly without animal protein with some vegan options. It is recommended to taste as input
 Sweetcorn exquisite cream served in panne cook seeds and mushrooms as the main course accompanied Beer
 with mashed potatoes, avocados, almonds and green banana. For dessert you can not miss trying Nutella and banana pudding or
 Flor de Milonga spectacular Jamaica, made with almond meringue with mascarpone cream and syrup Jaimaca flower.
 As a vegan option found Shawarma plate, flat bread stuffed with hummus, tabbouleh, falafel and wash.\n\n
 Address: Cra 35 # 8A-3, Provensa, Medellin.       \nTeléfono: (4) 4440935
    </string>
    <string name = "rumba1t"> Disco Prizma </string>
    <string name = "rumba1"> Disco only reggaeton. It is huge, and open space is a relief. The capacity of the club is 700 people.
 Prizmas popularity means that it is best to book in advance through his Facebook page, instead of the
 planning a Friday night or Saturday and expect to get.\n\nAddress: Calle 25 A # 43 B - 199, Barrio Colombia\n
 Phone: 231-2313\nWebsite: http://www.facebook.com/pages/PRIZMA-MEDELL%C3%8DN/168164453238584\n
 Email: prizmadiscoteca@hotmail.com\n
    </string>
    <string name = "rumba2t"> Kukaramakara </string>
    <string name = "rumba2"> It is a place where people for the warm, fun and family atmosphere delita also enjoys an innovative
 atonement every night Latin lives are live performances accompanied by the best rumba of the city.
 It also has a wide variety of spirits, cocktails and cuisine that make the place an unforgettable experience
       \n\n Address: Cra 43A No. 6S - Rio 26 South 7th floor, El Poblado\n Tel. 57 (4) 312 25 27
    </string>
    <string name = "rumba3t"> Fonda sweet Jesus Mio </string>
    <string name = "rumba3"> We are a mountaineer inn, the best characterization of a typical village of Antioquia, with singers
 and artists live and characters, it is not uncommon that visitors encounter the fool of the people, the doctor, the priest
 and the schoolgirl among others, these characters make the moments in our facilities are the most pleasant, filling each attendee
 of joy and enjoyment\n SWEET JESUS MIO "as you so Paisa"\n\nDirección. Carrera 38 No. 19 255 km2 palms immediately via
 the courtyard restaurant, Medellin\nTeléfono: (4) 4,446,022
    </string>
    <string name = "turis1t"> Museum of Antioquia </string>
    <string name = "turis1"> This is the most important museum in Medellin, and one of the best known of Colombia.
 It was first founded in the department of Antioquia, the second in the country. Collections rest in the center of Medellin,
 collection of works dating back to 1954 by national and international artists. against Botero Square, near the Parque Berrio Metro Station.
       \n\n Address:. Cl 52 # 52-43, Medellin, Antioquia\n Tel .: (4) 2,513,636
    </string>
    <string name = "turis2t"> Tourist Corridor Las Palmas </string>
    <string name = "turis2"> Your semicampestre environment, the striking designs of facilities and easy access from anywhere
 in Medellin give this place a touch only. This tourist circuit corresponds to the first kilometers of the route Las Palmas,
 which begins near the subway station Exhibitions. In this modern way prestigious restaurants, clubs, bars, cafes and estaderos
 are located, with offers for all audiences. Due to the nature of the route, which climbs a hillside surrounding the city, most
 establishments possible to see the city, which gives them an additional attraction. Either the purpose or the nightlife
 space for lunch or dinner in this tourist circuit Las Palmas visitors can find a varied offer that satisfies everyone.
       \n\n Via Las Palmas
    </string>
    <string name = "turis3t"> Metro Tourism </string>
    <string name = "turis3"> Tourism METRO is a program created to travel the Aburrá Valley and nearby regions, exploring the nuances
 that characterize it: flowers, culture , trade, art and mountains rich in a wide variety of species. Their packages give you the
 opportunity to explore their interest through a means of insurance, flexible, reliable and friendly transportation environment;
 it is also an international leader.\n\n For prices, can contact 4449598 Hi METRO line and to purchase the tour package,
 come to one of the Customer Service Points * -PAC- located at stations Niquía, San Antonio and Itagui. Each package includes
 the means of payment to access the METRO system and transportation to the site you have chosen.
    </string>
</resources>